HANEEN NASEREDDIN

Tinley Park, IL | 708-336-1771 | haneennasereddin1@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Skilled Account Executive & Marketing Graduate with over 4 years of experience in building effective, intuitive strategies, as well as leveraging techniques to promote products, services, and public image, in a variety of industries. Extensive experience in reaching out to the market and cultivating customers' interests in products/services in ways that strengthen the company's reputation and facilitate continuous growth. Contributing to the planning and execution of advertising and promotional marketing campaigns, while also enhancing engagement through social media channels. Continually exceeds expectations by creating valuable partnerships and works well with people at all levels of the organization, including stakeholders, customers, vendors, and team members.

Skills

- Conducting Market & Competitor Research
- Creating Awareness & Developing the Brand
- Targeting Audiences & Building Relationships
- Designing Marketing Materials & Writing Copy
- Sourcing & Securing Sponsorships
- Initiating & Controlling Customer Surveys

- Influencing, Negotiation & Interpersonal Skills
- Monitoring Campaign Metrics & Progress
- Budget Management & Cost Controls
- Maintaining & Updating Customer Databases
- Enthusiastic & Goal-Oriented Team Player
- Bilingual English & Arabic Communication

Work History

Account Executive 01/2020 to 03/2021

Yelp - Chicago, IL

- Owning, managing, and working with a diverse pipeline of clients, ranging from Restaurant Owners to Dentists, while working collaboratively with cross-functional teams to drive revenue growth with new customers.
- Becoming an expert in the company's solutions and adapting product recommendations to suit clients' needs by asking
 probing questions, as well as effectively handling objections to close the deal.
- Consulting, educating, strategizing, and successfully selling advertising programs through a high volume of sales calls, strong communication, and tenacity, while gaining mastery of the company CRM, Salesforce.
- Creating impactful sales presentations to demonstrate how company products can be leveraged to connect with consumers, including profile restructuring and upgrades to improve engagement and enhance customer flow by 10-50%.
- Successfully selling an array of options to better optimize clients' accounts, consistently exceeding monthly sales quotas by 13% and contributing to overall team targets, while engaging with the Executive team for complex sales scenarios.
- Collaborating with Marketing to develop and implement digital marketing and advertising strategies, and participating in training sessions to help the agency become more proficient in building/executing effective marketing campaigns.
- Tracking, measuring, and analyzing key account metrics such as customer conversion rates, impression shares, average order value, and cost-per-click, in order to optimize digital campaigns from an ROI perspective for accounts.

Assistant Manager 06/2016 to 12/2019

Massage Envy – Orland Park, IL

- Came aboard as a Sales Consultant, increasing customer retention by ~15% by building lasting relationships, managing
 marketing initiatives and promoting membership, and providing outstanding customer service at all times.
- Successfully exceeded all sales and membership sign-up goals by 34% and 10%, respectively, for over a year, which resulted in receiving a promotion in 11/2018, becoming the youngest AM in the firm's history.
- Supported the Franchise Owner in setting and achieving membership and retail sales/profitability goals, as well as partnered with the Owner to regularly monitor progress against these goals.
- Developed a culture that embraced and reflected the brand's core values, resulting in a 62% higher employee satisfaction rate and a 45% improvement in productivity, which led to an 86% increase in client retention.

- Delivered an optimal experience for upwards of 50 members and hundreds of guests daily through the proper management of Human Resources functions, including conducting interviews and onboarding training for new staff.
- Effectively oversaw and managed key daily business operations of the franchised location, including inventory, marketing, and bank deposits, as well as processed payroll and performed associated recordkeeping.
- Developed staff schedules to ensure streamlined workflow, improving efficiencies by 46%, and coordinated a team of 8, including handling performance evaluations, leading to far-exceeding clinical goals by 30% and personal sales by 23%.

Academic Projects

Chicago ToolBank, Chicago, IL - 08/2018 to 11/2018

• Built and presented a sustainable business model for the Chicago ToolBank, and designed a functioning business plan to maintain a sustainable revenue stream.

Sid Feldman Legacy Fund, Chicago, IL - 01/2019 to 04/2019

• Organized a fundraising event in which 100% of the profits went towards the Fund, while also gaining mastery of the class CRM.

Education

DePaul University - Bachelor of Science in Marketing, Chicago, IL - 06/2019

- Developed tactical and strategic marketing skills, including analyzing and solving market problems, while deepening
 understanding of how marketing delivers value to customers and businesses.
- Successfully developed abilities in marketing management, focusing on information gathering analysis, strategic planning, and tactical decision-making, as well as learned how to best create and implement marketing strategies.
- Completed courses in international, mobile, social media, and internet marketing, along with new product development, consumer behavior, and quantitative methods.
- Gained the skillset to distinguish features and benefits of products and services in order to create an impactful value proposition, while understanding how external factors and demographic change affects demand.
- Efficiently collected, analyzed, and interpreted data, including acquiring knowledge of the functional areas of and the interrelationships within the business, as well as recognized legal/ethical issues.
- Created a comprehensive marketing plan and used marketing methodologies and tools, along with analytical and reflective skills, to develop strategic plans.

Moraine Valley Community College – Associate of Science, Palos Hills, IL – 12/2017